[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":21914,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":984310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":996219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1784,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":998007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":4027,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":1002035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2192,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":1004229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5637,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":1009868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2364,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":1012235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5386,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":1017624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1581,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":1019208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If th e sum is  6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3838,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":1023047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1097,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":1024147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3006,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":1027154,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1195,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":1028351,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2114,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":1030469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1581,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":1032055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br / > (Remem ber, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3306,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":1035364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1153,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":1036519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":1038948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1223,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":1040173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3273,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":1043448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1100,"trial_type":" feedback ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":1044550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":10265,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":1054825,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity unde r +<sub> 6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":9727,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":1064554,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":11687,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":1076243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3716,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":1079962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub >? <br / ><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":1083170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":8401,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":1091575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":1096010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1331,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":1097343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":1100194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1491,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":1101689,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1104038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3933,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1107973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"fre e","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":25218,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1133193,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":7454,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1140650,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6< /sub> 1  +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":19518,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1160170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":11948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1172121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but t here is  no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1390,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1173513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3009,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1176525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub>  using 5","rt":1934,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1178462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5980,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1184445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1234,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1185680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1187341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1805,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1189149,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":21267,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1210417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10323,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1220743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1224556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1372,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1225932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1231077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1236550,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7956,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1244509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1248267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4113,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1252382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. 4 plus 1 is 5","response_history":["5. 4 plus 5 is 4","5. 4 plus 1 is 5"],"rt":23047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1275431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3.  8 plus 4 is 12 minus 9","response_history":["1","3.  8 plu ","3.  8 plus 4 is 12 minus 9"],"rt":37490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1312924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0? That was the identity last time","response_history":["0? Thta","0? Tht","0? That as","0? That a","0? That wa ","0? That was the identity lst","0? That was the identity last time"],"rt":56192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1369119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":" free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1376356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3059,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1379418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. 9 minus 6 is 3","response_history":["6. 9 minus 6 is 3"],"rt":16715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1396138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your an swer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no. I cant think of a combination to make 8","response_history":["no.. ","no..","no. 2 plus 1 would","no. 2 pl","no. 2 p","no. 2 ","no. 2","no. ","no.","no. I cant think of a combu","no. I cant think of a combination to maaake 3","no. I cant think of a combination to maake 3","no. I cant think of a combination to make 3","no. I cant think of a combination to make 8"],"rt":127875,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1524018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes. It makes all numbers 1-9","response_history":["yes","no. I cant think of a combination that wouks","no. I cant think of a combination that wouk","no. I cant think of a combination that woul ","no. I cant think of a combinatio n that w oulf","no. I cant think of a combination that would make ","yes. It makes all numbers 1-9"],"rt":76078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1600098,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no. I cant think of a combination  to make 8","response_history":["no. I cqn","no. I cq","no. I cant think of a combination  to make 8"],"rt":84874,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1684975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes. i can make all numbers ","response_history":["no i cant mae ","no i cant mae","no i cant make an 8","no i cant make an ","yes. i can ma ke all n umbes","yes. i can make all numbers "],"rt":45656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1730633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":10050,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1740685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","response_history":["1-","1","n-1"],"rt":15575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1756263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is  the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x thats how it went before","response_history":["n-x thats how it went before"],"rt":25592,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1781858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"not that i can think of","response_history":[" ","not that i can think of"],"rt":27564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1809425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":" multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":8905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1818333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["False","True"],"rt":7189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1825524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":24763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1850291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True  or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"false. generators were prime numbers","response_history":["now thqt ","now thqt","now thq","now that i thinkk maybe tha ","now that i thinkk maybe that wa","now that i thinkk maybe that ws ","now that i thinkk maybe that ws","now that i thinkk maybe that was tge ","now that i thinkk maybe that was tge","now that i thinkk maybe that was tg","now that i thinkk maybe that was the pattern","now that i think maybe that was the pattern","now that i thik maybe that was the pattern","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 3 ","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 3","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 6 is divisibleee ","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 6 is divisibleee","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 6 is  divisibl ee","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 6 is divisible by ","now that i think maybe that was the pattern, 6 is div","now that i think maybe that was the patte","x","false. generati","false. generators were prim ","false. generators were prime numbers"],"rt":224429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2074722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Never","Sometimes"],"rt":13616,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2088344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please exp lain in  words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"5 plus 5 is 10 minus 6 (the original n) is 4 which was not ","response_history":["3 ","3","5 Pl","5 P","5 plus 5 is 10 minus 6 (tye ","5 plus 5 is 10 minus 6 (tye","5 plus 5 is 10 minus 6 (ty","5 plus 5 is 10 minus 6 (the original n) is 4 which was not "],"rt":108876,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2197224,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Never","Sometimes"],"rt":10658,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2207886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to  ask you  some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1375,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2209263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":2546,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2211811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree","Associates Degree"],"rt":3232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2215046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"statistics","response_history":["statistics"],"rt":9188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2224237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2231206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5417,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2236624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2608,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2239236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this  HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2241438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2243824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2245377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are you r native  language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":6402,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2251781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3631,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2255414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":4931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2260347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]